<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tower_of_sorcerer</string>
    <string name="game_title1">Tower of the</string>
    <string name="game_title2">Sorcerer</string>
    <string name="new_game">New Game</string>
    <string name="load">Load</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="back_btn_alert">Do you want to exit the game?</string>
    <string name="game_over_title">Game Over</string>
    <string name="game_over_message">Good luck on your next try.</string>
    <string name="saint_2f">Thank you so much for saving me. I can increase your attack and defense power by 3 percent. Do you want me to do it now?</string>
    <string name="saint_3f">Alas, my age is catching up to me. I can fight no more. Brave young man,
you should take this Staff of Wisdom since I have no use for it. It will reveal
the strength of monsters so you could better prepare your fight against them. Take
care and good luck.</string>
    <string name="saint_4f">There are doors which cannot be opened with a key. To open them, you will have
 to defeat the monsters which guard them.</string>
    <string name="saint_6f">After you make a purchase from a merchant, go talk to him again because he
will tell you some important information.</string>
    <string name="saint_16f">I heard that there are two hidden red keys hidden in this area.</string>
    <string name="saint_16fh">Back</string>
    <string name="saint_18f">Many knights had failed to pass this area because of those Rock Monsters.
Their defenses are just too high. Maybe you should increase your offense at the
altar a few time in this area.</string>
    <string name="saint_21f">Do you know the Archmage in this area is the owner of this tower? He is way
too strong for you now. Fighting him is suicide. You should go to higher floors
and get stronger first.</string>
    <string name="saint_23f0">It is said that there is a hidden message in this floor.</string>
    <string name="saint_23f1">Go 0F!</string>
    <string name="saint_27f">At this current stage, if you have 1500 health, 80 attack, 98 defense, 5
yellow keys and 1 blue key, you are almost ideal.</string>
    <string name="saint_31f">The attack power of the swordsmen is too high. You should only fight them when
you can one shot them, or you will lose a lot of health.</string>
    <string name="saint_33f">More haste, less speed.</string>
    <string name="saint_36f">If you find the four secret tunnels in this floor, you will be able to go
upstairs without fighting strong enemies.</string>
    <string name="saint_37f">This floor is an item warehouse, but to get the treasure, you will have to use
the mattock.</string>
    <string name="saint_39f">At three o\'clock, the secret treasure which allows you to teleport three time
will appear.</string>
    <string name="saint_42f">The magic powers of Mages allows them to attack from a distance, so don\'t get
near them. The magic power of Demon Sergeant cannot work alone, but when they
appear in pairs, they can form an invisible demon gate which cut your health in
half when you pass by.</string>
    <string name="saint_45f">The 44th floor is in a different dimension, and you can\'t get there with
stairs. But you may try to teleport.</string>
    <string name="saint_46f">There is a secret about the 41st floor - it is perfectly symmetrical even
though it doesn't seem to be.</string>
    <string name="saint_48f">The shape of five on a dice is actually an ancient symbol for sealing magic.
Remember the symbol because it will help you in the future.</string>
    <string name="saint_default">Good luck young man!</string>
    <string name="merchant_2f0">Thank you so much for freeing me. Please take this 1000 gold as a gift.</string>
    <string name="merchant_6f0">I have a blue key for 50 gold. Would you like to buy it?</string>
    <string name="merchant_7f0">I have 5 yellow keys for 50 gold. Would you like to buy them?</string>
    <string name="merchant_12f0">I have a red key for 800 gold. Would you like to buy it?</string>
    <string name="merchant_12fh">I have lots of yellow keys, 1000 gold each. Would you like to buy one?</string>
    <string name="merchant_15f0">I have a blue key for 200 gold. Would you like to buy it?</string>
    <string name="merchant_28f">Would you like to sell your yellow keys to me for 100 gold each. I need lots of them.</string>
    <string name="merchant_31f0">I have 1 blue key and 4 yellow keys for 1000 gold. Would you like to buy them?</string>
    <string name="merchant_38f0">I have 3 yellow keys for 200 gold. Would you like to buy them?</string>
    <string name="merchant_39f0">I have 3 blue keys for 2000 gold. Would you like to buy them?</string>
    <string name="merchant_45f0">I can recover you 2000 health for 1000 gold. Would you let me do it?</string>
    <string name="merchant_47f0">I have a enhanced mattock for 4000 gold. Would you like to buy it?</string>
    <string name="merchant_2f1">Thank you. Good luck on your journey</string>
    <string name="merchant_6f1">This tower consists of 50 floors. Every 10 floors form one area, and each area
 has one boss guarding the entrance to the next area. To proceed, you must defeat
 these bosses.</string>
    <string name="merchant_7f1">When you offer gold in exchange for strength at an alter, you should put your
priority on defense. However, you cannot completely ignore offense either.</string>
    <string name="merchant_12f1">Have you found the secret tunnels on the 9th, 16th, and 18th floor? I heard
that there are more of them on higher floors.</string>
    <string name="merchant_15f1">When you carry a cross, your attacks will be twice as effective against
zombies and the Vampire, and I don\'t think you can defeat the Vampire without it.
There is a cross hidden on a floor higher than this one.</string>
    <string name="merchant_31f1">Even though the tower is said to have 50 floors, I have never heard anyone
reaching to the 50th floor.</string>
    <string name="merchant_38f1">There is never a gate without Gate-Keepers, and there is always a gate when
you see Gate-Keepers.</string>
    <string name="merchant_39f1">There is a Lucky Gold hidden in this tower. If you carry it with you, you will
get twice as much money from battles.</string>
    <string name="merchant_45f1">I heard that the Sacred Shield can protect you against all kinds of magic
powers. But I also heard that this shield is hidden on a floor which doesn't
exist.</string>
    <string name="merchant_47f1">I heard that to kill the Dragon, you must have a holy sword, a holy
shield, and most importantly the Dragonsbane, which doubles your attack against
the Dragon.</string>
    <string name="merchant_default">Keep it secret, and don\'t tell others</string>
    <string name="purchase_fail">You don\'t have enough gold.</string>
    <string name="purchase_fail_28f">You don\'t have any yellow key.</string>
    <string name="princess_dialog1">I am fake. See you on 50th floor.</string>
    <string name="princess_dialog2">I am fake. See you on 50th floor.</string>
    <string name="echo_btn1"> 4F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn2"> 6F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn3"> 6F Merchant</string>
    <string name="echo_btn4"> 7F Merchant</string>
    <string name="echo_btn5">12F Merchant</string>
    <string name="echo_btn6">15F Merchant</string>
    <string name="echo_btn7">16F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn8">18F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn9">21F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn10">27F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn11">31F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn12">31F Merchant</string>
    <string name="echo_btn13">33F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn14">36F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn15">37F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn16">38F Merchant</string>
    <string name="echo_btn17">39F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn18">39F Merchant</string>
    <string name="echo_btn19">42F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn20">45F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn21">45F Merchant</string>
    <string name="echo_btn22">46F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn23">47F Merchant</string>
    <string name="echo_btn24">48F Saint</string>
    <string name="no_echo">Echo has not been collected yet.</string>
    <string name="staff_of_echo_menu_select">Choose an echo to listen</string>
    <string name="background_picture">Backgroud Picture</string>
    <string name="wake_up">. . . \t\t. . . \t\tup. . . \t\twake up. . .</string>
    <string name="thief0">Who am I? I am a thief, and I\'m looking for a treasure in this tower. Even though I was caught, it\'s not a big deal you know?
        \'cause I just need to spend a few nights digging tunnels and I will be out of here. And you are such a lucky dog, bro. \'cause I have just
        finished the tunnel planning to get out, and you were thrown in my cell. Follow me and let\'s get out!</string>
    <string name="thief1">Forgot to tell you, but you should have figured out by now that your weapons were taken away. It\'s not wise to fight monsters
        without any weapons. I know there is one old iron sword on the 5th floor, and one old iron shield on the 9th floor. I ain\t gonna call them good
        weapons but still, better than nothing, right? By the way, I have dug many tunnels in this tower. I covered them to look just like regular walls,
        but if you are able to find them, they will help you a lot. Good luck bro. See ya.</string>
    <string name="thief2">Oh wow! You are much stronger than I thought, bro. You killed the Skeleton Captain and his soldiers all by yourself? Damn,
        that\'s amazing. You know thers is a silver sword on 17th floor, right? Good luck finding it. I got to go. See ya.</string>
    <string name="thief3">Wow, look at who is here! The Skeleton Captain Slayer! Did the giant octopus block your way? It\'s such a pain in the ass!
        I counld\'t get around it so I had to dig this tunnel. You came just in time. Enjoy this free tunnel. See you later!</string>
    <string name="thief4">Yo, bro. Nice to see ya. Sigh, I am out of luck. Can\'t find my treasure anywhere. I\'m taking some rest.</string>
    <string name="thief5">Thank you so much for saving me bro! Thought I was doomed. I got caught again, but this time they saw my mattock and took
        it away, so I can\'t dig tunnels to get out. But you came and saved me. I can\'t thank you enough. Is the Dragon on the 35th floor blocking your
        way? Don\'t you worry bro. I got your back. I have hidden my other mattocks in the tower. Let me find one frist and I will dig a tunnel for you
        so you can get around the Dragon.</string>
    <string name="thief6_1">Give me some time to find my hidden mattocks, bro. I will catch you up on the 35th floor.</string>
    <string name="thief6_2">Just follow the tunnel I have dug for you, and you will be on your way upstairs. After this incident, I realized that it\'s
        not worth risking my life looking for some treasures which may not even exist. I\'m outta here. Good luck saving the princess. Goodbye.</string>
    <string name="thief7">i am devil zeno1</string>
    <string name="thief8">i am devil zeno2</string>
    <string name="thief9">i am devil zeno3</string>
    <string name="thief10">i am devil zeno4</string>
    <string name="thief11">i am devil zeno5</string>
    <string name="thief12">i am devil zeno6</string>
    <string name="Load_img_description">Load Activity Image</string>
    <string name="Load_default">----</string>
    <string name="Load_floor_number">-- F</string>
    <string name="item_description_cross">Passive item. It doubles your attack when you are fighting against zombies and vampires.</string>
    <string name="item_description_elixir">It can be used only once. It increases your health points by 10 x Attack + 5 x Defence. Would you like to use it now?</string>
    <string name="item_description_mattock">It can be used only once. It destroys the walls next to you. Would you like to use it now?</string>
    <string name="item_description_wing_center">It can be used 3 times. It teleports you to an unoccupied space which is symerical to the center of the current floor. Would you like to use it now?</string>
    <string name="item_description_enhanced_mattock">It can be used only once. It destroys all the walls at the current floor. Would you like to use it now?</string>
    <string name="item_description_bomb">It can be used only once. It destroys all the monsters standing next to you, but it does not work against bosses. Would you like to use it now?</string>
    <string name="item_description_wing_up">It can be used only once. It teleports you to one floor above the current floor when you are next to the stairs. Would you like to use it now?</string>
    <string name="item_description_enhanced_key">It can be used only once. It opens all the yellow doors at the current floor. Would you like to use it now?</string>
    <string name="item_description_wing_down">It can be used only once. It teleports you to one floor below the current floor when you are next to the stairs. Would you like to use it now?</string>
    <string name="item_description_lucky_gold">Passive item. It doubles the money you get from battle.</string>
    <string name="item_description_dragonsbane">Passive item. It doubles your attack when you are fighting against the Dragon.</string>
    <string name="item_description_snow_crystal">Passive item. It freezes lava into solid ground.</string>
    <string name="item_title_cross">Cross</string>
    <string name="item_title_elixir">Elixir</string>
    <string name="item_title_mattock">Mattock</string>
    <string name="item_title_wing_center">Magic Wing - Center</string>
    <string name="item_title_enhanced_mattock">Enhanced Mattock</string>
    <string name="item_title_bomb">Bomb</string>
    <string name="item_title_wing_up">Magic Wing - Up</string>
    <string name="item_title_enhanced_key">Enhanced Yellow Key</string>
    <string name="item_title_wing_down">Magic Wing - Down </string>
    <string name="item_title_lucky_gold">Lucky Gold</string>
    <string name="item_title_dragonsbane">Dragonsbane</string>
    <string name="item_title_snow_crystal">Snow Crystal</string>
    <string name="zeno_3f">Another interloper coming for the princess! Sergeants, throw him in jail!</string>
    <string name="skeleton_captain_10f_1">You are trapped!!! Soldiers, go kill him!!!</string>
    <string name="vampire_20f_1">I am vampire!!!</string>
    <string name="archmage_25f">Archmage says fight me!</string>
    <string name="knight_captain_32f_1">Knight captain says fight me!</string>
    <string name="knight_captain_32f_2">see you later</string>
    <string name="knight_captain_40f_0">You think I am that easily defeated? You must be kidding me! What you just killed were merelly illusions. Now, it\'s
    my turn to kill you!</string>
    <string name="knight_captain_40f_1">You can never defeat me! Skeleton Elites, charge!</string>
    <string name="knight_captain_40f_2">Charge! Knight squad! Go kill him!</string>
    <string name="knight_captain_40f_3">charge 3</string>
    <string name="knight_captain_40f_4">He is weak now! Knight Elites, charge!!!</string>
    <string name="knight_captain_40f_5">You angered me so much! You should really turn away and run because I am going to kill you myself!</string>
    <string name="knight_captain_40f_6">Don\'t you dare following me! I\'m going to call some backups, and you doomed</string>
    <string name="knight_captain_42f_1">Oh! Lord Zeno! I. . . I am. . . I am not able to defeat this man. P. . . Ple. . . Please forgive me.</string>
    <string name="zeno_42f_1">You are far too weak. You are no longer of any use. Sergeants, kill him!</string>
    <string name="knight_captain_42f_2">No. Please, Lord Zeno. Please. Aaahh!!!</string>
    <string name="zeno_42f_2">Zeno blablabla</string>
    <string name="zeno_49f_1">You can\'t defeat me cause i am zeno</string>
    <string name="zeno_49f_2">What? You created the symbol sealing away my magic power? You still won\'t defeat me though I only get 1/10 of my power.</string>
    <string name="pick_up_red_crystal">Picked up Red Crystal. Attack + </string>
    <string name="pick_up_blue_crystal">Picked up Blue Crystal. Defense + </string>
    <string name="pick_up_red_potion">Picked up Red Potion. Health + </string>
    <string name="pick_up_blue_potion">Picked up Blue Potion. Health + </string>
    <string name="pick_up_iron_sword">Picked up Iron Sword. Attack + 10</string>
    <string name="pick_up_iron_shield">Picked up Iron Shield. Defense + 10</string>
    <string name="pick_up_silver_sword">Picked up Silver Sword. Attack + 20</string>
    <string name="pick_up_silver_shield">Picked up Silver Shield. Defense + 20</string>
    <string name="pick_up_knight_sword">Picked up Knight Sword. Attack + 40</string>
    <string name="pick_up_knight_shield">Picked up Knight Shield. Defense + 40</string>
    <string name="pick_up_divine_sword">Picked up Divine Sword. Attack + 50</string>
    <string name="pick_up_divine_shield">Picked up Divine Shield. Defense + 50</string>
    <string name="pick_up_sacred_sword">Picked up Sacred Sword. Attack + 100</string>
    <string name="pick_up_sacred_shield">Picked up Sacred Shield. Defense + 100. Immune to magic attacks.</string>
    <string name="pick_up_stf_echo">Picked up Staff of Echo. It allows you to listen to information given by Merchants and Saints again.</string>
    <string name="pick_up_stf_space">Picked up Staff of Space. It teleports you to floors you have already visited when you are next to the stairs.</string>
    <string name="pick_up_cross">Picked up Cross. It doubles your attack when you are fighting against zombies and vampires.</string>
    <string name="pick_up_mattock">Picked up Mattock. It destroys the walls next to you.</string>
    <string name="pick_up_wing_cent">Picked up Magic Wing - Center. It teleports you to an unoccupied space which is symerical to the center of the current floor.</string>
    <string name="pick_up_bomb">Picked up Bomb. It destroys all the monsters standing next to you, but it does not work against bosses.</string>
    <string name="pick_up_wing_up">Picked up Magic Wing - Up. It teleports you to one floor above the current floor when you are next to the stairs.</string>
    <string name="pick_up_enhanced_key">Picked up Enhanced Yellow Key. It opens all the yellow doors at the current floor.</string>
    <string name="pick_up_wing_down">Picked up Magic Wing - Down. It teleports you to one floor below the current floor when you are next to the stairs.</string>
    <string name="pick_up_lucky_gold">Picked up Lucky Golde. It doubles the money you get from battle.</string>
    <string name="pick_up_dragonsbane">Picked up Dragonsbane. It doubles your attack when you are fighting against the Dragon.</string>
    <string name="pick_up_snow_crystal">Picked up Snow Crystal. It freezes lava into solid ground.</string>
</resources>
