<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tower_of_sorcerer</string>
    <string name="game_title1">Tower of the</string>
    <string name="game_title2">Sorcerer</string>
    <string name="new_game">New Game</string>
    <string name="load">Load</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="start_button">START</string>
    <string name="exit_button">EXIT</string>
    <string name="btn_newgame">New Game</string>
    <string name="btn_exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="levelSelect">Select Maze</string>
    <string name="finished_title">Congrats</string>
    <string name="loser_title">You Lose</string>
    <string name="finished_text">Game Over</string>
    <string name="finished_button">End Game</string>
    <string name="info_button">Info</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="saint_2f">Back</string>
    <string name="saint_3f">Alas, my age is catching up to me. I can fight no more. Brave young man,
you should take this Staff of Wisdom since I have no use for it. It will reveal
the strength of monsters so you could better prepare your fight against them. Take
care and good luck.</string>
    <string name="saint_4f">There are doors which cannot be opened with a key. To open them, you will have
 to defeat the monsters which guard them.</string>
    <string name="saint_6f">After you make a purchase from a merchant, go talk to him again because he
will tell you some important information.</string>
    <string name="saint_16f">I heard that there are two hidden red keys hidden in this area.</string>
    <string name="saint_16fh">Back</string>
    <string name="saint_18f">Many knights had failed to pass this area because of those Rock Monsters.
Their defenses are just too high. Maybe you should increase your offense at the
altar a few time in this area.</string>
    <string name="saint_21f">Do you know the Archmage in this area is the owner of this tower? He is way
too strong for you now. Fighting him is suicide. You should go to higher floors
and get stronger first.</string>
    <string name="saint_23f">It is said that there is a hidden message in this floor.</string>
    <string name="saint_27f">At this current stage, if you have 1500 health, 80 attack, 98 defense, 5
yellow keys and 1 blue key, you are almost ideal.</string>
    <string name="saint_31f">The attack power of the swordsmen is too high. You should only fight them when
you can one shot them, or you will lose a lot of health.</string>
    <string name="saint_33f">More haste, less speed.</string>
    <string name="saint_36f">If you find the four secret tunnels in this floor, you will be able to go
upstairs without fighting strong enemies.</string>
    <string name="saint_37f">This floor is an item warehouse, but to get the treasure, you will have to use
the mattock.</string>
    <string name="saint_39f">At three o\'clock, the secret treasure which allows you to teleport three time
will appear.</string>
    <string name="saint_42f">The magic powers of Mages allows them to attack from a distance, so don\'t get
near them. The magic power of Demon Sergeant cannot work alone, but when they
appear in pairs, they can form an invisible demon gate which cut your health in
half when you pass by.</string>
    <string name="saint_45f">The 44th floor is in a different dimension, and you can\'t get there with
stairs. But you may try teleporting.</string>
    <string name="saint_46f">There is a secret about the 41st floor - it is perfectly symmetrical even
though it doesn't seem to be.</string>
    <string name="saint_48f">The shape of five on a dice is actually an ancient symbol for sealing magic.
Remember the symbol because it will help you in the future.</string>
    <string name="saint_default">Good luck young man!</string>
    <string name="merchant_2f0">Thank you so much for freeing me. Please take this 1000 gold as a gift.</string>
    <string name="merchant_6f0">I have a blue key for 50 gold. Would you like to buy it?</string>
    <string name="merchant_7f0">I have 5 yellow keys for 50 gold. Would you like to buy them?</string>
    <string name="merchant_12f0">I have a red key for 800 gold. Would you like to buy it?</string>
    <string name="merchant_12fh">I have lots of yellow keys, 1000 gold each. Would you like to buy one?</string>
    <string name="merchant_15f0">I have a blue key for 200 gold. Would you like to buy it?</string>
    <string name="merchant_28f">Back</string>
    <string name="merchant_31f0">I have 1 blue key and 4 yellow keys for 1000 gold. Would you like to buy them?</string>
    <string name="merchant_38f0">I have 3 yellow keys for 200 gold. Would you like to buy them?</string>
    <string name="merchant_39f0">I have 3 blue keys for 2000 gold. Would you like to buy them?</string>
    <string name="merchant_45f0">I can recover you 2000 health for 1000 gold. Would you let me do it?</string>
    <string name="merchant_47f0">I have a enhanced mattock for 4000 gold. Would you like to buy it?</string>
    <string name="merchant_2f1">Thank you. Good luck on your journey</string>
    <string name="merchant_6f1">This tower consists of 50 floors. Every 10 floors form one area, and each area
 has one boss guarding the entrance to the next area. To proceed, you must defeat
 these bosses.</string>
    <string name="merchant_7f1">When you offer gold in exchange for strength at an alter, you should put your
priority on defense. However, you cannot completely ignore offense either.</string>
    <string name="merchant_12f1">Have you found the secret tunnels on the 9th, 16th, and 18th floor? I heard
that there are more of them on higher floors.</string>
    <string name="merchant_15f1">When you carry a cross, your attacks will be twice as effective against
zombies and the Vampire, and I don\'t think you can defeat the Vampire without it.
There is a cross hidden on a floor higher than this one.</string>
    <string name="merchant_31f1">Even though the tower is said to have 50 floors, I have never heard anyone
reaching to the 50th floor.</string>
    <string name="merchant_38f1">There is never a gate without Gate-Keepers, and there is always a gate when
you see Gate-Keepers.</string>
    <string name="merchant_39f1">There is a Lucky Gold hidden in this tower. If you carry it with you, you will
get twice as much money from battles.</string>
    <string name="merchant_45f1">I heard that the Sacred Shield can protect you against all kinds of magic
powers. But I also heard that this shield is hidden on a floor which doesn't
exist.</string>
    <string name="merchant_47f1">I heard that to kill the Dragon, you must have a holy sword, a holy
shield, and most importantly the Dragonsbane, which doubles your attack against
the Dragon.</string>
    <string name="merchant_default">Keep it secret, and don\'t tell others</string>
    <string name="purchase_fail">You don\'t have enough gold.</string>
    <string name="purchase_fail_28f">You don\'t have any yellow key.</string>
    <string name="princess_dialog">I am fake. See you on 50th floor.</string>
    <string name="echo_btn1"> 4F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn2"> 6F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn3"> 6F Merchant</string>
    <string name="echo_btn4"> 7F Merchant</string>
    <string name="echo_btn5">12F Merchant</string>
    <string name="echo_btn6">15F Merchant</string>
    <string name="echo_btn7">16F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn8">18F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn9">21F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn10">27F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn11">31F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn12">31F Merchant</string>
    <string name="echo_btn13">33F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn14">36F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn15">37F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn16">38F Merchant</string>
    <string name="echo_btn17">39F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn18">39F Merchant</string>
    <string name="echo_btn19">42F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn20">45F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn21">45F Merchant</string>
    <string name="echo_btn22">46F Saint</string>
    <string name="echo_btn23">47F Merchant</string>
    <string name="echo_btn24">48F Saint</string>
    <string name="no_echo">Echo has not been collected yet.</string>
    <string name="staff_of_echo_menu_select">Choose an echo to listen</string>
    <string name="background_picture">Backgroud Picture</string>


</resources>
